When you come in this room, you get
goosebumps. [music]
These things have a a an aura about them
that you can't see through a [__]
camera. This one appears to be free
spinning. I am here with a massive trove
of artifacts. And it comes off. Can see
no glue, no mortar, no nothing. That I
was told dates between 44 and 48,000
years [music] of age. Watch this one.
Has like a magnetic catch in it. Does it
light up? Want me to look at these
things and extrapolate what I can tell
from them? They had three calendars.
They were far more advanced than we
were. and they were obsessed with time.
I'm going to go through piece by piece
and show you what I see here and tell
you what I think. You think about the
type of [music] intelligence these
humans had to carve a base relief in a
slab of stone like this. If you're smart
enough to do that and not even have an
oops, what else do you know? [music] And
why are you spending your time carving a
rock?
[laughter]
Shout out to Graham Hancock for teaching
me all this. Graham, I'd love for you to
come down here with me and look at this.
This is the most amazing [__] I've ever
seen. Thanks to Graham, I know about the
Mayan clocks. They had two different
clocks, uh, one for the Earth and one
for the sun, I believe. And they
operated independently with a a
different spheroid inside of a spheroid
to calculate a date. They had one for
each and then where they intersected
would give another date. They had three
calendars. They were far more advanced
than we were. And they were obsessed
with time. at the height of their
empire, [music] the the Mayans were
killing 250,000 people a year, human
sacrifice to stave off the end of the
world. And they also studied the
heavens. And as soon as I saw this, I
was like, "Hey, this does something."
So, I want you to see this one appears
to be free spinning and it comes off and
it it doesn't really have anything
special that I can tell, but watch this
one. It has like a magnetic catch in it.
You see that? Watch.
It's magnetic.
There's something in there that makes it
go backward. Or if it's right here,
watch. It'll go on its own.
Okay. I've looked at so many damn pieces
of electrical equipment. I see circuit
boards more than anything else. And I
realized that [music] this probably does
something extremely important.
The level of skill required to make
this. And I don't even know how they
have them set. When I first saw it, I
tried to take this off cuz I thought
it'd come off. I wasn't trying [music]
to break it, but it is on there. And I
can see no glue, no mortar, no nothing
in any of this. It's like it's fused in
there. [music]
And I mean the skill required to cut a
piece of stone that flat, that smooth,
[music] and that circular to fit inside
this is just beyond me. So when I see
this, I automatically recognize that
somebody far more [music] intelligent
than me made it. And you know,
intelligent people don't do [__] for no
reason. If you're real [__] smart,
you know what you're doing. You're
you're you're conscious. This had to
have taken a long time to make. And I
want to know why. When I think about the
significance of the Mayan clocks and the
fact that [music] this was found in
Mayan territory, I'm thinking, "Wow,
this is probably going to move on its
own, depending on what these clocks say
if this thing is wound correctly." And I
make the comparison of this. You see
this? This does a lot. You know, you can
send money with this. You know, you can
contact other planets.
Maybe you can contact other countries.
You can FaceTime. You can see things
from far with this, but it has to have
service and energy to operate. And
[music] if something happened on planet
Earth and there was 10,000 years past,
society was gone, big war, nuclear
winter, [music] somebody found a cell
phone, they wouldn't know what it did at
all. And they never would because
there's no service anymore. There's no
connection. There's no electricity
[music] coming out of an outlet with a
type-C connector. I think this is the
same thing. This definitely does
something. Um,
and I mean [music] just to be around it,
like when you come in this room, you get
goosebumps. Things have a a an aura
about them that you can't see through a
[__] camera, but it's the realest
thing you'll ever feel. I think this
thing is some kind of [music] tool that
could point to like, you know, a certain
point in time or a certain place on
Earth. Maybe this is how they found
sacred [music] sites. Um, you know, off
of the magnetism of Earth and the
seasons. [music] Cuz if you look, I
don't know what these say, but they say
something. [music]
Everything in here was done
purposefully. And look, a fish. There's
a lot [music] of astrological symbols
and things that look kind of like alien
saucers. Um,
so this is definitely a tool, a clock of
some [music] kind. Um, needs to be
studied further. The black light test.
Does it light up?
It's got little No. [music]
No. That's all external. Not this one.
[music] This one does not light up, but
others do.